<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>GoldenGate on amardeepsidhu.com</title><link>https://examplesite.com/category/goldengate/</link><description>Recent content in GoldenGate on amardeepsidhu.com</description><generator>Hugo -- 0.135.0</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2013 20:32:33 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://examplesite.com/category/goldengate/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Oracle GoldenGate 11g Handbook</title><link>https://examplesite.com/blog1/2013/07/18/oracle-goldengate-11g-handbook/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2013 20:32:33 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://examplesite.com/blog1/2013/07/18/oracle-goldengate-11g-handbook/</guid><description>&lt;p>Few months ago I contributed a chapter (on Monitoring, Troubleshooting and Performance tuning) to a GoldenGate book on Oracle Press that &lt;a href="http://robertgfreeman.blogspot.in/">Robert Freeman&lt;/a> was authoring. Thought of posting a small update that the book is now out. My name doesn’t appear on the main page &lt;img loading="lazy" src="http://amardeepsidhu.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2013/07/wlEmoticon-sadsmile.png" alt="Sad smile" />
but you will see it in the Acknowledgements section &lt;img loading="lazy" src="http://amardeepsidhu.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2013/07/wlEmoticon-winkingsmile.png" alt="Winking smile" />
Below is a screenshot taken from Amazon preview &lt;img loading="lazy" src="http://amardeepsidhu.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2013/07/wlEmoticon-smile.png" alt="Smile" />
.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>You may want to grab a copy if you are using/planning to use Oracle GoldenGate 11g.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Configure GoldenGate Extract to read from remote logs</title><link>https://examplesite.com/blog1/2012/05/26/configure-goldengate-extract-to-read-from-remote-logs/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2012 18:13:02 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://examplesite.com/blog1/2012/05/26/configure-goldengate-extract-to-read-from-remote-logs/</guid><description>&lt;p>Sometimes you may need to run GoldenGate on some different machine than the one that hosts the database. It is very much possible but some kind of restrictions apply. First is that the Endian order of both the systems should be same and the second is the bit width has to be same. For example it is not possible to run GoldenGate on a 32 bit system to read from a database that runs on some 64 bit platform. Assuming that the environemnt satisfies the above two conditions; we can use the LOGSOURCE option of TRANSLOGOPTIONS to achieve this.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Tuning GoldenGate Extract Pump performance</title><link>https://examplesite.com/blog1/2012/05/25/tuning-goldengate-extract-pump-performance/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2012 20:38:18 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://examplesite.com/blog1/2012/05/25/tuning-goldengate-extract-pump-performance/</guid><description>&lt;p>Just a quick note/post about the significance of COMPRESS and TCPBUFSIZE parameter in performance of a GoldenGate Extract Pump process. COMPRESS helps in compressing the outgoing blocks hence helping in better utilization of the bandwidth from source to target. GG is going to uncompress the blocks before writing them to the remote trail file on the target. Compression ratios of 4:1 or better can be achieved. Of course, use of COMPRESS may result in increased CPU usage on both the sides.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>