<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Blog1s on amardeepsidhu.com</title><link>https://examplesite.com/blog1/</link><description>Recent content in Blog1s on amardeepsidhu.com</description><generator>Hugo -- 0.135.0</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2014 16:04:56 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://examplesite.com/blog1/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>VirtualBox and Windows driver verifier</title><link>https://examplesite.com/blog1/2014/12/03/virtualbox-and-windows-driver-verifier/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2014 16:04:56 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://examplesite.com/blog1/2014/12/03/virtualbox-and-windows-driver-verifier/</guid><description>&lt;p>I was troubleshooting some Windows hangs on my Desktop system running Windows 8 and enabled driver verifier. Today when I tried to start VirtualBox it failed with this error message.&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Failed to load VMMR0.r0 (VERR_LDR_MISMATCH_NATIVE)&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>Most of the online forums were asking to reinstall VirtualBox to fix the issue. But &lt;a href="http://stackoverflow.com/questions/21654596/suddenly-getting-failed-to-load-vmmr0-r0-verr-ldr-mismatch-native-in-virtual">one of the thread&lt;/a> mentioned that it was being caused by Windows Driver Verifier. I disabled it, restarted Windows and VirtualBox worked like a charm. Didn’t have time to do more research as i quickly wanted to test something. May be we can skip some particular stuff from Driver Verifier and VirutalBox can then work.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Oracle GoldenGate 11g Handbook</title><link>https://examplesite.com/blog1/2013/07/18/oracle-goldengate-11g-handbook/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2013 20:32:33 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://examplesite.com/blog1/2013/07/18/oracle-goldengate-11g-handbook/</guid><description>&lt;p>Few months ago I contributed a chapter (on Monitoring, Troubleshooting and Performance tuning) to a GoldenGate book on Oracle Press that &lt;a href="http://robertgfreeman.blogspot.in/">Robert Freeman&lt;/a> was authoring. Thought of posting a small update that the book is now out. My name doesn’t appear on the main page &lt;img loading="lazy" src="http://amardeepsidhu.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2013/07/wlEmoticon-sadsmile.png" alt="Sad smile" />
but you will see it in the Acknowledgements section &lt;img loading="lazy" src="http://amardeepsidhu.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2013/07/wlEmoticon-winkingsmile.png" alt="Winking smile" />
Below is a screenshot taken from Amazon preview &lt;img loading="lazy" src="http://amardeepsidhu.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2013/07/wlEmoticon-smile.png" alt="Smile" />
.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>You may want to grab a copy if you are using/planning to use Oracle GoldenGate 11g.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Oracle database 12c</title><link>https://examplesite.com/blog1/2013/06/27/oracle-database-12c/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2013 07:28:45 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://examplesite.com/blog1/2013/06/27/oracle-database-12c/</guid><description>&lt;p>So there is a new toy in the market for database geeks : Oracle has released database 12c. Every social platform is abuzz with the 12c activity. So thought that I should also complete the ritual &lt;img loading="lazy" src="http://amardeepsidhu.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2013/06/wlEmoticon-winkingsmile.png" alt="Winking smile" />
&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In &lt;a href="http://blog.aristadba.com/?p=254">this post&lt;/a> Aman has already summed up many important links.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Maria Colgan has posted some useful links &lt;a href="https://blogs.oracle.com/optimizer/entry/oracle_database_12c_is_here">here&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>And &lt;a href="http://apex.oracle.com/pls/apex/f?p=202202:2:::::P2_SUCHWORT:migrate12c">here is a link&lt;/a> to a slidedeck about Upgrading and Migrating to 12c.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Happy 12c’ing !&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>agent deployment error in EM 12c</title><link>https://examplesite.com/blog1/2013/06/16/agent-deployment-error-in-em-12c/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2013 22:34:56 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://examplesite.com/blog1/2013/06/16/agent-deployment-error-in-em-12c/</guid><description>&lt;p>Yesterday I was configuring EM 12c for a Sun Super Cluster system. There were a total of 4 LDOMs where I needed to deploy the agent (Setup –&amp;gt; Add targets –&amp;gt; Add targets manually). Out of these 4 everything went fine for 2 LDOMs but for the other two it failed with an error message. It didn’t give much details on the EM screen but rather gave a message to try to secure/start the agent manually. When I tried to do that manually the secure agent part worked fine but the start agent command failed with the following error message:&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Updating to Exadata 11.2.3.1.1</title><link>https://examplesite.com/blog1/2012/08/19/updating-to-exadata-11-2-3-1-1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Aug 2012 22:37:41 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://examplesite.com/blog1/2012/08/19/updating-to-exadata-11-2-3-1-1/</guid><description>&lt;p>Just a quick note about change in the way the compute nodes are patched starting from version 11.2.3.1.1. For earlier versions Oracle provided the minimal pack for patching the compute nodes. Starting with version 11.2.3.1.1 Oracle has discontinued the minimal pack and the updates to compute nodes are done via Unbreakable Linux Network (ULN).&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Now there are three ways to update the compute nodes:&lt;/p>
&lt;p>1) You have internet access on the Compute nodes. In this case you can download patch &lt;strong>13741363&lt;/strong>, complete the one time setup and start the update.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>ORA-01422 while compiling objects</title><link>https://examplesite.com/blog1/2012/07/31/ora-01422-while-compiling-objects/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2012 22:04:28 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://examplesite.com/blog1/2012/07/31/ora-01422-while-compiling-objects/</guid><description>&lt;p>There was an interesting issue at one of the customer sites. Few tables in the database were altered and the dependent objects became invalid. But the attempts to compile the objects using utlrp.sql or manually were failing. In all the cases it was giving the same error:&lt;/p>
&lt;pre tabindex="0">&lt;code>SQL&amp;gt; alter function SCOTT.SOME_FUNCTION compile;
alter function SCOTT.SOME_FUNCTION compile
*
ERROR at line 1:
ORA-00604: error occurred at recursive SQL level 1
ORA-01422: exact fetch returns more than requested number of rows
ORA-06512: at line 27
SQL&amp;gt;
&lt;/code>&lt;/pre>&lt;p>At first look it sounded like some issue with the dictionary as the error in case of every object (be it a view, function or package) was the same.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Configure GoldenGate Extract to read from remote logs</title><link>https://examplesite.com/blog1/2012/05/26/configure-goldengate-extract-to-read-from-remote-logs/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2012 18:13:02 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://examplesite.com/blog1/2012/05/26/configure-goldengate-extract-to-read-from-remote-logs/</guid><description>&lt;p>Sometimes you may need to run GoldenGate on some different machine than the one that hosts the database. It is very much possible but some kind of restrictions apply. First is that the Endian order of both the systems should be same and the second is the bit width has to be same. For example it is not possible to run GoldenGate on a 32 bit system to read from a database that runs on some 64 bit platform. Assuming that the environemnt satisfies the above two conditions; we can use the LOGSOURCE option of TRANSLOGOPTIONS to achieve this.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Tuning GoldenGate Extract Pump performance</title><link>https://examplesite.com/blog1/2012/05/25/tuning-goldengate-extract-pump-performance/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2012 20:38:18 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://examplesite.com/blog1/2012/05/25/tuning-goldengate-extract-pump-performance/</guid><description>&lt;p>Just a quick note/post about the significance of COMPRESS and TCPBUFSIZE parameter in performance of a GoldenGate Extract Pump process. COMPRESS helps in compressing the outgoing blocks hence helping in better utilization of the bandwidth from source to target. GG is going to uncompress the blocks before writing them to the remote trail file on the target. Compression ratios of 4:1 or better can be achieved. Of course, use of COMPRESS may result in increased CPU usage on both the sides.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>